hello and welcome to my presentation on
您好，欢迎来到我的演讲
transport layer security 1.3 which is a
传输层安全1.3
new security feature in JDK 11 my name
我的名字叫JDK 11中的新安全功能
is Sean Mullen and I'm a member of the
是肖恩·马伦（Sean Mullen），我是
security libraries team at Oracle so
Oracle的安全库团队
first that some background let's start
首先，让我们开始一些背景
with a brief overview of TLS TLS is a
TLS的简要概述TLS是一个
standard protocol for allowing clients
允许客户使用的标准协议
and servers to securely to communicate
和服务器进行安全通信
securely over the Internet it provides
通过它提供的Internet安全地
the security properties of
的安全属性
confidentiality authenticity and
机密性，真实性和
integrity TLS is most commonly used by
完整性TLS最常用于
web browsers and web servers to secure
网络浏览器和网络服务器以确保安全
data sent over the Internet the JDK
JDK通过Internet发送数据
includes implementations of various
包括各种实现
versions of the SSL and TLS protocols
SSL和TLS协议的版本
specifically SSL version 3 TLS version
特别是SSL版本3 TLS版本
1.0 and 1.2 d TLS which is the Datagram
1.0和1.2 d TLS，即数据报
version of TLS version 1.0 and 1.2 and
TLS版本1.0和1.2的版本以及
now with jdk 11 TLS version 1.3
现在带有jdk 11 TLS版本1.3
note that SSL v3 is widely considered
请注意，SSL v3被广泛认为
insecure and unsafe to use and it's
使用起来不安全，不安全，
disabled by default in the jdk when
默认情况下，在jdk中禁用
using TLS in your java applications you
在您的Java应用程序中使用TLS
can use the java x net and java x net
可以使用java x net和java x net
ssl packages into java dot base module
ssl包到Java点基础模块
these are lower level api's for using
这些是使用的较低级别的api
SSL and TLS and are often referred to as
SSL和TLS，通常称为
JSF II or the Java secure socket
JSF II或Java安全套接字
extension if you are using HTTP and you
扩展名（如果您使用的是HTTP）
want to establish a secure connection
想要建立安全的连接
using HTTPS you can now use the new JDK
使用HTTPS，您现在可以使用新的JDK
11 HTTP client API which is in the Java
Java中的11个HTTP客户端API
net HTTP package in the java.net HTTP
java.net HTTP中的net HTTP包
module
模组
so why do we need another version of TLS
那么为什么我们需要另一个版本的TLS
why do we need TLS 21.3 let's take a
为什么我们需要TLS 21.3，让我们
brief look at some of the issues that
简要看看一些问题
these protocols have had over the years
这些协议多年来
first Excel v3 has multiple
第一个Excel v3具有多个
vulnerabilities and it's formally
漏洞，这是正式的
deprecated in RFC seven five six eight
RFC中弃用的七五六八
it should no longer be used in practice
它应该不再在实践中使用
the TLS protocols have had many
TLS协议有很多
challenges over the last 20 or so years
最近20年左右的挑战
RFC 747 gives a really good summary of
RFC 747很好地总结了
these attacks and it's interesting to
这些攻击，有趣的是
see TLS versions 1.0 and 1.1 are both
请参阅TLS版本1.0和1.1都
now quite old and are rapidly being
现在很老，正在迅速
phased out TLS version 1.2 is the
逐步淘汰TLS版本1.2是
current TLS best practice but it itself
当前的TLS最佳做法，但它本身
is also fairly old about 10 years old so
大约还十岁，所以
there was general consensus that it
人们普遍认为
needed to be updated with more modern
需要更新以更现代
and latest crypto practices in
和最新的加密实践
advancements so TLS 1.3 was about four
进步，因此TLS 1.3大约有四个
years in the making it was recently
多年的发展是最近
published in August 2000 18 as RFC 84
2000年8月发布18为RFC 84
for six
六个
TLS 1.3 is a major overhaul of the TLS
TLS 1.3是TLS的一项重大改进
protocol with two primary benefits
协议有两个主要好处
enhanced security and improved speed
增强安全性并提高速度
let's take a look at each of those
让我们来看看每个
improvements in a bit more detail so
更详细的改进
enhance security less is safer
增强安全性越安全
TLS 1.3 removes support for outdated
TLS 1.3删除了对过时的支持
cryptography which improves the security
加密技术，可提高安全性
and makes it less likely a session can
并减少了会话可以
be broken because of an insecure cipher
由于密码不安全而被破坏
suite or some other form of weak
套房或其他形式的弱者
cryptography that was used the removal
删除使用的密码学
of the cryptograph outdated cryptography
密码过时的密码学
includes such functionalities such as
包括诸如
static RSA and diffie-hellman key
静态RSA和diffie-hellman密钥
exchange CBC mode ciphers md5 and sha-1
交换CBC模式密码md5和sha-1
hash function
哈希函数
Triple DES and rc4 ciphers and arbitrary
三重DES和rc4密码以及任意
diffie-hellman groups TLS 1.3 also
diffie-hellman也将TLS 1.3分组
removes unsafe features such as
删除不安全的功能，例如
compression and renegotiate this is not
压缩并重新协商这不是
a complete list you should see the RFC
完整列表，您应该会看到RFC
and other online literature for other
和其他在线文学
features I've been removed or simplified
我已被删除或简化的功能
in general TLS 1.3 supports fewer and
通常，TLS 1.3支持更少的
more modern crypto algorithms
更现代的加密算法
it adds support for RSA SSA - PSS
它增加了对RSA SSA-PSS的支持
signature algorithm the cha-cha 20 and
签名算法cha-cha 20和
poly 1 305 stream ciphers the x2 55 1 9
poly 1305流加密x2 55 1 9
and X 4 for 8 with the curve
X 4表示8
diffie-hellman key agreement mechanism
diffie-hellman密钥协商机制
and the Edwards curve digital signature
和Edwards曲线数字签名
algorithm all of these are more modern
算法所有这些都更现代
cryptographic algorithms that are more
加密算法更多
efficient and more secure
高效，更安全
teyla's 1.3 is also faster than previous
teyla的1.3也比以前更快
versions of the TLS protocol it has a
TLS协议的版本
completely new handshake module which
全新的握手模块
requires fewer round trips TLS 1.2
需要更少的往返TLS 1.2
requires two round trips for a complete
需要两次往返才能完成
handshake
握手
however TLS 1.3 uses one round trip by
但是TLS 1.3使用一次往返
default and optionally with pre-shared
默认值，并且可以选择预先共享
keys can use a 0 round trips so here are
键可以使用0往返，所以这里是
some details about the TLS 1.3
有关TLS 1.3的一些详细信息
implementation in JDK 11 this feature
在JDK 11中实现此功能
was defined in jet 332 and the goal of
是在喷射332中定义的，目标是
the jet was to produce an interoperable
喷气机将产生一个可互操作的
TLS 1.3 implementation supporting all of
TLS 1.3实施支持所有
the required features as of heard for
所需的功能
the RFC
RFC
the implementation therefore does not
因此，实现不
support many of the optional features as
支持许多可选功能，例如
specified in the RFC however many of
在RFC中指定，但是许多
those optional features are considered
这些可选功能被认为
important and and will hopefully be
重要，并且有望成为
added in subsequent releases of the JDK
在JDK的后续版本中添加
there are no new api's that we had to
没有我们必须的新的api
add to support jdk TLS 1.3
添加以支持jdk TLS 1.3
implementation so therefore you use the
实现，因此您使用
same job api's when using TLS 1.3 as you
与您使用TLS 1.3时相同的作业API
did for previous TLS versions however
但是对于以前的TLS版本
there are some new algorithm names there
那里有一些新的算法名称
is now a TLS V 1.3 as a cell context
现在是TLS V 1.3作为单元上下文
algorithm and a TLS V 1.3 protocol and
算法和TLS V 1.3协议，以及
there are two new cipher suites both of
有两个新的密码套件
which are requirements of the RSC there
这是RSC的要求
is one new security property named JDK
是一个名为JDK的新安全属性
TLS key limits and you can use this to
TLS密钥限制，您可以使用它来
limit the amount of data an algorithm
限制算法的数据量
may encrypt with a specific set of keys
可以使用一组特定的密钥进行加密
and here's an example the property value
这是一个属性值示例
consists of the name of the algorithm in
由以下算法的名称组成
this case AES GCM no padding followed by
在这种情况下，AES GCM没有填充，后跟
a key update which is the TLS message
密钥更新即TLS消息
that will be sent once the limit is
一旦达到限制，就会发送
reached and then the limit itself which
达到然后极限本身
is
是
integer value in either bytes or as a
整数值（以字节为单位）或
power of two
二的幂
TLS 1.3 is enabled by default on both
默认情况下，两者均启用TLS 1.3
the client and server sides so there's
客户端和服务器端，所以
nothing you need to do to specifically
您不需要做任何专门的操作
enable it it will be used if both sides
启用它，如果双方都使用
support it
支持它
there are a few compatibility issues
有一些兼容性问题
that you may encounter when upgrading to
升级到
TLS 1.3 you should check the release
TLS 1.3您应该检查发布
notes for the Jeff to see if any of
给Jeff的笔记，看看是否有
these issues may affect your application
这些问题可能会影响您的应用程序
so next steps we encourage you to
因此，下一步我们鼓励您
download JDK 11 at the following URL
通过以下URL下载JDK 11
ww Oracle comm / Java download you can
ww Oracle comm / Java下载即可
also join the open JDK that website and
也加入开放的JDK网站
follow us on Twitter for more
在Twitter上关注我们以了解更多
information at open JDK handle or using
打开JDK句柄或使用时的信息
hash tag job 11 or you can also follow
哈希标签作业11或您也可以关注
me at my Twitter handle Shawn J Mullen I
我在我的Twitter处理Shawn J Mullen I
often tweet a lot about Java security so
经常发布有关Java安全性的很多文章，因此
it's a good way to keep up with what's
这是跟上最新进展的好方法
happening in that area
发生在那个地区
thank you
谢谢
[Music]
[音乐]